[{"answer": "I believe the people of Iowa are smart enough that they can see the difference between somebody who's trying to help the country and somebody who is simply running a negative campaign.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 5, "question": "Are attack ads the price of admission in politics?", "qSentId": 4}, {"answer": "Well, it's working for a variety of reasons, Piers, but what I'd satisfy is this.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "Would you agree?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "Well, there's durability in Newt's numbers based on what you've shown.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "What's your reading of these fluctuations?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "Not all of it.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "Yes, it's, as I said, lacerating, but it also has the benefit of being factually correct, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Not all of it.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "Would you dispute any of the details?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "Sure, so Governor.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "Jump in there?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "Well, if anybody wants to know Newt's views on anything go to Newt.org.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "What is Newt Gingrich's view of this apparently intransigent position by the Republicans which is causing endless grief to everybody?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "Isn't it time for a president who looks like a 1970s game show host?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "Well, you know, first of all, none of these candidates are perfect.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "Isn't part of the problem for Mitt Romney is that people do look at him and think '70s game show host?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "Governor Pawlenty, we really don't want to have the debate, do we, about which candidate in this field has changed their mind?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "Let me start with you, Mary Matalin, I mean is it too late for Sarah Palin?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Not technically.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "Technically is it too late?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "Well, I would say this about Sarah Palin.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "I mean is the field still open or are they in the end going to choose now from what would appear to be a narrowing field?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "I think that we are on a collision course with a Ron Paul victory in the Iowa caucuses.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "Knowing the lay of the land there, how do you see things panning out in the next couple of weeks?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "I mean the way this has been structured now this year coming up with New York and California, a song coming much later, this process could go on for months and months and months with the leadership changing quite dramatically, couldn't it?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "I think it's really the words you used, character.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "Well, what makes him special is his will to win, his drive, his desire.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "And what makes him special?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "HITAKER: Right.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "What is wrong with a God-fearing guy who goes out, works hard, you know, does his job but believes in God and sends a positive message?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "Well, because of his skill set and his athleticism, he can get away from the rush and can he buy time and he does get more time to throw than a lot of other quarterbacks, but he's still learning the position and that's what people have to understand.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "I mean, am I wrong about that or is that a particular talent that he has that is putting him slightly above the others at the moment?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "I love you, too.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "OK?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "Yes, Lord, whatever you command.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "But, just take it down a notch, will you, buddy?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "It's really not.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "I mean, if you're a young person watching football right now, Tebow magic isn't going to do you any harm, is it?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "Well, they need one more win to get into the playoffs, and I know Tim wants to deliver that.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "How's he going to do?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "I think he'll deal with it great.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "How far is he going to go, do you think, and how will he deal with it?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "It is, but I think that really has to do with his faith, too.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "I mean, that's what's making him the sort of people's hero, isn't it?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "You are.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "Am I know doing the Tebow?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "Well, I --", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "And what does this bring me?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "Would you wait.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "What's the matter now?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, thank you very much.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "Do you get as much of a thrill out of the very, by comparison, very boring process of making a movie?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "Even if I tell you what I -- we get in the ring and I do boxing with him --", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "Are you prepared to reveal number of press-ups and number of stomach crunches you can achieve?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "And that's where I think you and I differ.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Do you, really?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "I'd be pretty careful where the gloves go.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "Everything you know about me, Kenneth, would you imagine I'm a fair fighter?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "Well, I have to say, I'm sorry it's a bit of a boring answer given what we're kind of talking about, but Olivier, I think, really does take some beating.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "Who has been, pound for pound, the greatest actor that you've ever seen in action?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "Well, I haven't done much of that.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "I mean, do you have the old Peter's friends, gang all get together?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "Oh, wow, you put me on the spot there, because I'm going to say, and please don't hate me for this being an obvious answer, but I just watched Michelle Williams, \"Close to,\" (ph), across the last picture we made from the most unlikely of the, this sort of fragile and petite, seeming, beautiful young woman, seemed to expand in the makeup chair as she filled out the curves of Marilyn, she found the voice, she occupied the face, the hair, the walk, which wasn't so much of a walk as a float, a shimmy through the movie.", "docId": "111220pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "Who's the one you'd choose for your last, ever role?", "qSentId": 575}]